[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard hello
welcome to the junkyard love podcast I
hope y'all are very well I hope you
taking care of yourself I hope you
loving yourself I hope you're learning
about yourself I hope you're educating
yourself about yourself over taking a
look at your thoughts I hope you taking
a look at your mind I hope you're
listening to your body I hope you're
looking at your situations and your life
in a holistic sense and also I hope that
you check out today's recommendation
which is closer to truth on YouTube it's
just a youtube channel closer to truth
Lawrence Krauss is a guy's name
he just kind of so he travels around
asking like existential questions to you
know neuroscientist and big-time
meditators and biologists and people who
attend like all these consciousness
conferences and super fascinating great
stuff
really nice scenic if you enjoy podcast
it's just people sitting there but they
have they do it outdoors in beautiful
places so it just has this extra
aesthetic the camera is always panning I
know it's just great closer to truth if
you enjoy the the essence of the
upcoming conversation the exploration of
consciousness and the cosmos and
mathematics and these sorts of things
philosophizing life check that out
closer truth on YouTube let's get
rolling with the episode please take
care of yourself I just hit record
minutes it's like we're trying to prove
any points and be like this is exactly
what we're going to talk about we're
just comes and it's Jake with the
junkyard love podcast
welcome everybody welcome carry it on
all righty
what's going on guys Brandon Cruz with
wild productions again to see Jake for
the first time in months and I gotta say
it is a serious serious pleasure
absolutely
I absolutely love my fiancee and my
roommate's but guy time it's like yeah
much needed
yes much needed you know bro time I mean
really just any interaction with friends
taking direction at all yeah just people
I'm happy I talked to myself a [__]
lot and at some point it's like I need
somebody to bounce this stuff off you
know yeah it's uh it's weird when you
start to like actually think of your
co-workers as like I didn't really like
them when I was like kind of seeing them
every day but now I kind of yeah I kind
of miss you kind of annoy me a little
bit Terry he's such a dick but I missed
that dick dude would you just talk to me
right now and just yeah let me scoff and
walk away
well somebody give me when Terry gives
me at work every day and you better wait
on put a wig on and act act for me like
it get mad at Lacey you're like you've
been so nice to me it's driving me
through the roof yes sir you reenact
everyone that I'm with at work so I feel
like I have purpose again I I mean I
could imagine that like if there are a
house full of actors somewhere probably
in California just like having a bunch
of props in sets and just being really
bored there their days are probably like
insane like they probably wake up as
like somebody's just like I'm a cowboy
today bro and you if you an actor to you
just play along
yeah you just playing along yes this is
a rodeo right now yo that would be a fun
way of life like live as if you're in a
sitcom kind of I don't get why sorry I
don't get why a lot of move that thing
oh you want a brownie I'm gonna I'm
man twist it a little bit right there
with that it sounds nice
pop it that's a good game right there I
actually just found that in my house as
we're like doing our little spring
cleaning they're not allowed to be
contacting other people and touching
them but you're just handing them an
object now you bop it I had the funniest
breath I had the funniest idea of like a
video where because 420 had passed
well obviously while quarantine is going
on and I could imagine like like some
people meeting their friends and like
kind of breaking the quarantine thing
but they're still kind of sketchy about
coronavirus so they decide like to load
a bowl and there's like handed off and
they're like you know take a hit its 421
wha
and they take a hit and they're like oh
[__] actually I don't want to get Corona
so you gotta kind of gotta clear that
whole balling yourself
oh and or like they like have like a
massive like cross joint or something
yeah and they're like ah I forgot like
that's all you man you guys and you're
just like a lightweight and you're just
like the vision gets all
interdimensional yeah I feel like the
laughs oh like a hole oh [__] and I sign
up for it's like when people talk about
like you have like like smoking weed
with horn massage before like bro I
smoked weed I smell smoke dogs weed and
I [__] died like you ever hear that
I've like I there's occasionally people
like Wiz Khalifa Snoop Dogg like yeah
Tommy Chong or something I think he was
mentioned like we're had everybody's
like yo I smoked with them and it was so
next level it's not even though it just
gets to a point where it's not even fun
it's like it takes the whole it's
actually like it I mean the same goes
for like drinking with friends that like
get really messed up no like you know go
to the bar and they're just getting
right shit-faced you're like yeah That's
not me
alright that's just no that's a whole
nother level where I just
I know I'm not gonna feel good you have
to do theirs once in a while I feel like
the last I don't know I really never
like to get [__] up like there's like
once in a while where you give it to
yourself and you prep for it almost like
you only get you're like alright Robin
I've been you just taking Metamucil
every day I've been drinking a gallon
and a half of water because I know that
I'm gonna have to take three days off
work or whatever especially my stomach
today to make sure I had enough room to
right you know fit all these shots in it
yeah you're prepping for it yeah it's
interesting well so I wanted to so we're
kind of talking about like the vibe of
the coronavirus so like but originally I
was it's so it's such an interesting
thing because things are you know
nonlinear and linear a lot of times in
how there's such thing as kind of like a
vibe like how things perceived so like a
lot of the like D platforming is like
stuff that happened in like 1995 that is
like it was not offensive back then that
a comedian said say and then they bring
it into the year 2020 and they're like
this is so offensive and it's like no
the vibe like the way our understanding
as a society of how things work has
changed since then so you can't like
back then it wasn't insane for this
person to say that whatever so I was
comparing that to the let's say March
for my area for our area I feel like it
was like March 14th was like everybody's
still going out everybody's still like
having a beer we're like yeah the ground
virus exists like I don't know what's
going on with it it seems crazy like oh
there's a couple cases here but like it
seems like it's mostly in China whatever
like it's like you're almost ignoring it
and then all of a sudden it's like I
don't for those news cycles are just
like everybody like took it seriously or
there was like some sort of news cycle
or news particularly story particular
story but uh March 14th to March like
16th was just shut down the whole know
it was like off so it's really
interesting to see so just using that
example like how quickly things change
and then thinking like so two weeks ago
like I wouldn't I wasn't this is the
first time that I've had somebody I'm
gonna had my friend Eric for a podcast
outside and it was like I feel like I
kind of addressed it but I wasn't fully
present I was like nervous about it I
was thinking about the virus
think about how close we should be
getting like all those sort of things
but now the vibe is is I wish I had a
more intellectual 4 - yeah yes Jesus but
it's it's just lifted like it's like it
like there's there's this [__]
attitude there's a lot of people who
have the whole time been like I don't
believe any of it
like and then there's but now there's
there's just this like well we've got to
carry on like we need each other we need
human interaction like so I feel like
for me and it feels weird to talk about
like I feel like I'm gonna like get in
trouble or people are gonna like judge
me or it's it's hard to have my own
opinion on this which is another weird
weird thing that I'm noticing that's
like everybody kind of feels like they
don't really want to unless they're one
of the people who are really loud and
like expressing it's not [__] real
mmm a lot of a lot of the other people
like I don't know like I just want to
like respect it and like let's just wait
it out but so so where I feel on it is I
have like select people that I'm going
to now see mmm
I have like a few people who I know
aren't in contact with a shitload of
other people as far as the podcast goes
I'm gonna just kind of make it to where
it's a beeline into the door like we try
not to touch it too much we try to just
like see some artists they are yeah like
so I'm trying to like tiptoe into it I'm
not trying to like just well I mean
obviously I'm trying to break the
[__] law for sure like so I don't
know what area I fall in like I'm not
specifically trying to like just follow
that I'm just trying to be intelligible
about the whole thing
trying to I'm trying to in the end back
to the vibes just what I just want to
meet there like I want to have the
conversations at the time where the vibe
is like like where the like what do we
what do we think about it like we don't
have to like act like we're not like
still a little nervous still a little
scared we don't have to act like we're
like we have to go back to work we're
exactly where we are so like where we
are on today what's it what's the date
me mmm 13 12 11 10 May 13th then I'll
try to post this one in a more timely
manner than I normally
but it's the vibe is we've chosen a few
friends a few people to see and be
around and I'm kind of curious for what
comes next
what where is where is your arrive and
what's your perspective on like the vibe
kind of situation that I was diamond if
you have a better word than vibe please
I love five five minutes like my
favorite word so I'm sure
vibing out it's just weird cuz there's
so many different variables to what is
going on and the amount of confusion and
the decisions decisions and confusion
stem from all the way from the top like
every day it seems like the people who
are running this country tell us
something and then the next day it's
something else and then you know it was
don't ever wear a mask because you could
be breathing in the bacteria now it's
always wear your mask you know and it's
this constant influx of misinformation
and information and it not necessarily
can be their fault but it also can be
their fault because it's like you're
telling some people to do something and
then telling them do something else and
half those people are like oh [__] you
guys like you're lying to me like Who am
I to trust if these people are telling
me what to do and they're wrong and my
people are dying and then you got other
people that are just like scared because
they have no idea what to do they're
just like I'm just gonna sit inside and
just wait this thing out then you got
people who just like completely don't
believe in it and don't care and then
you got like the the people who are just
like kind of like you and I ish we're
we're like trying to test our foot in
the water and like see if like turning
there's a smart I think we do need to
start implementing smart ways to
interact with each other like we're both
young I don't leave the house hardly
ever
and I social distance from so many
people I don't go and go to the store
and go do this and go see family and all
that stuff like we keep our distance so
I feel like mice for myself I'm a safe
bet
to hang out with the interactions aren't
gonna spread and that's another thing is
the people that don't believe that this
disease exists it is a very real and
physical disease it actually exists it's
an it's something that my roommates a
nurse she's seen people die from it so
we don't know I mean we know as much as
we can know about it but this there's a
lot that we don't know about yeah yeah
that's where we're just kind of clueless
together as what it is like it I don't
know I I don't personally I've never
been someone who like needs to point
blame I suppose but blame is kind of a
way you know when you could find
somebody who is who you could point a
finger at and come consume your time
talking about like oh it's these peoples
fault or this person could have done
better or blame is a place of comfort
like for our you know um you know more
primitive mind like it's it's like like
some people do not like maintaining the
Unknowing which let's say nobody does
like nobody likes to do not know what's
gonna come next like you know we're all
kind of in this position of like what
the [__] is gonna happen like oh I know
what that are completely like I'm up for
the randomness but for the vast majority
of people we all need a story stick to
man and it's it's you know i I've you
know and I've had to remember that with
myself what I've also had to have
patience with myself when I'm
interacting with other people because
because I have to remember like this
person is just scared they're just
scared that's the root of this they're
scared just as much as I am you know
maybe more maybe less whatever like
they're they they have different
information maybe they have the same
information they have different life
experiences so this makes them a little
more unsettled like you know someone who
has been poor as a kid they're a little
more stressed out about maybe going
hungry again
and someone who's never like felt that
you know I mean like everybody has
different life experiences we're all at
a different level and what really you
know honestly pisses me off is that we
have a WWE [__] sideshow going on for
our political [__] no I'm not trying to
dive in a political stuff it's just like
I don't know I I just you know I see I
work I work audio work for like student
organizations and we was first started
up in Seattle I was working for an
organization and there was kids in the
room that were under 18 and their
framing of questions to the adults in
the room was there they're terrified man
like they don't know they should be able
to look to somebody at a podium not to
lie to them because nowadays we're
[__] smart you can't just be like
everything's gonna be fine if you just
believe like there needs to be
explanations these kids are smart they
understand what's going on you can't
just [__] them but I don't know I to
me I don't know man we just need
somebody who's a leader we need people
who are leaders we need you know this is
where the the American is taught to look
up to the president and in this way like
I'm not saying this is like he signs
this and this is his absolute duty but
I'm just saying that's what happens like
as a kid you should be able to look up
to leader and he kind of gives you some
answers that aren't [__]
he kind of tells you like hey you know
we don't know fully that's just the
truth and we're really trying our best
to figure it like he he helps comfort
you like when I was at this conference
these kids were asking the adults like I
just was in the room hearing it and
they're terrified and it pisses me off
and I wish that we had adults in the
[__] room is its death another
summarize I wish that we had adults in
the room for our political situation
like like these people there's there's
other people that are suffering besides
the ones who are pissed about suffering
like like the I just there's young kids
who are looking up to older people for
answers I'm sure of it and the older
people are just acting out ridiculous
[__] well you have the media notoriously
now is being labeled as a like rage bait
clickbait sort of
a company that is just trying to entice
the president you know politicians
forcing a narrative and just kind of
extracting as much of whatever they're
trying to extract from you know the
confrontation conflict a fear into the
American people's eyes whatever the case
may be
excuse me that's going on you're getting
a reaction from a president that is more
than willing to play the game you know
with these reporters with all this stuff
and meanwhile like you said you have
people that are seriously worried like
my kids don't eat because I don't make
enough I work two jobs I don't make
enough to feed my kids they usually eat
at school like I need to know what's
going on so that they can then begin to
eat again like I'm trying my best
it might not be like that in every
situation sometimes there might be an
abusive father there might be some crazy
situations going on but there are people
struggling right now and we need a
serious serious leader we need a person
who is a person you know for the longest
time I can't I can't even think of
besides like maybe Obama and bits like
where I felt where I wasn't watching a
robot talk you know and that speech of I
will do this for you guys and you will
be happy American you're saying like
what they said it's good to say rather
than like speaking yeah creating new
words with your mouth as a human that
move and advance us forward as humanity
and and people know [__] like there
are so many of us in the world now there
the internet is full of just
information and you can't escape it by
having a certain cadence of talking and
tone of voice and things like that it's
we literally can see and feel emotion
like humans see and feel emotion like
we're supposed to do you need to be a
man you need to be a person in charge a
leader in a community you need to be the
[__] king of a tribe you need to
literally take on this and be like hey
this is tough
we're gonna get through this we're doing
everything we can like bear with us
let's go I think that I mean you know
just our particular president and it's
not like just picking on trumpet
particularly but just seeing the
inability for us to actually interact so
if you watch the press conferences I saw
just this is a headline that I'm
repeating I did not watch the whole
thing so I might be speaking with but
but taking the situation to expand what
I thought the the person the journalist
the reporter asking him the question
asked kind of like a dumb question and I
framed it from a certain perspective
question and pissed him off and he
walked out this is what I heard
yesterday but so what we have is not
only someone who doesn't know how to
handle those things and a way of
handling them but like the what's
happening I think is outside of the
words themselves like and that's what
people don't understand like Trump
wasn't mad at exactly what this woman
seems to us said it's about he knows
that he knows right what does that mean
he knows it's a feeling of vibe that he
knows that she's actually kind of just
trying to be snarky so so he gets mad
and goes off and says the wrong thing so
it's that gotcha journaling is what they
call it a thing but like so we're not
actually on the surface we have this WWE
thing happening where we're in this in
the arena and there's fans cheering and
we're we're using the words themselves
to make headlines to sell to make these
things to make fear tactics to make a
drama for people to interact with
but somehow what's being unseen is is
there's a lot of people should know that
that reporter was also trying to get the
person on the podium to react a certain
way and when we have these assumptions
when we walk up to each other with these
assumptions this is kind of something
that I've referenced you this will make
sense the the garbage analogy or like
the homeless personality like you walk
up to your grandma with open arms your
shoulders are back and you're you're
smelling like you don't cover your nose
kind of but if you walk up to a homeless
stranger you're not gonna be like ready
to hug the guy you're gonna be kind of
put off you don't know I'm he's a
stranger yeah right so your vibe when
you walk up to your grandma and the vibe
when you walk up to a homeless person
you've never met what's happening is
they're all our political system seems
to be it's such a [__] broad a bunch
of homeless people ya know but they're
interacting at the the they're
interacting at the I'm treating you as a
homeless person before you even say
anything but they the news headlines and
what they're feeding the public is the
words themselves so there's two things
going on the same thing when you're
driving on the freeway you're going 75
and you just kind of get a weird kind of
feeling and you look over to your ride
out the window and there's a guy looking
at you and he's going 76 and he's
passing you like you sense it it's a
weird we don't know more than different
[__] big old metal boxes traveling
down a freeway like the the the vibe
again the feeling the thing that's like
really reality is like being ignored and
we're just listening to the words so
like what needs to happen in those
situations that we have leaders who are
willing to like dude we need to [__]
look at these things sensibly there
needs to be somebody who can come in and
be like Trump you literally need control
of your emotions right like in who knew
like if only it was that easy right but
there needs to be some sense waking
sense making or some sensible way for
somebody some sort of like intelligent
not just one [__] Messiah person like
just a new way of thinking a new not a
left and not a try
and not anything that opposes any of
those things but like hey guys our [__]
is so advanced at this point in the way
that we're all interacting but not
interacting we're all talking over each
other and at each other and not and
through each other in all these weird
ways there needs to be some developed
democracies what it needs to be it needs
to be developed it we're running a
system that's an old system we're
running on computers that are like
breaks you know what I mean like we
haven't changed the political system
ever to evolve to what it needs to be
the presidency is not now something that
one person should be tasked with
responsibility for the the u.s. alone is
massive massive markets massive trading
massive worldwide conflicts massive
everything and we're supposed to be the
leaders of the world apparently we're
supposed to be checking every country in
the world and making sure that everyone
is being safe and doing the right thing
and you know not making nuclear bombs
and [__] like that how are you going to
medieval not enslaving their people how
are you supposed to have one man speak
for all the actions of the US make
decisions for all the actions of the
u.s. understandably that it's not just
what he says goes but I mean he took out
a terrorist without anybody knowing just
one day just woke up and were like a
terrorist is blowing up could cause a
World War 3 you know it potentially
could have luckily it didn't but how is
one man that gives a nod on something
like that not expressed to the US where
we are private citizens that elect
public officials hmm but yet they're
acting private and we're acting public
it's the it's completely switched around
and and more to where they work in
secrecy and we work right out in the
open
yeah dude and it's so crazy that we the
way that we have formulated things is
people who talk up about it are kind of
like the rebels and kind of like the
like the the conspiracy theories in a
way right like it like the like the
don't ask questions thing is we're in a
time I think that that's like boiling
over like we're just we're just too
[__] smart like Millennials and
younger no it's a dude there's just a
lot more information now and if you are
doing noir smarts abroad work yeah yeah
it's a it's just hard to ignore the fact
that sorry to cut you off know the fact
that there are no reliable information
sources like right what used to be your
bread and butter for information CNN
MSNBC whatever the case may be they're
constantly wrong you've got independent
journalists on Facebook Instagram
YouTube you know patreon whatever it is
saying their side of the story and I
mean like most people are like scrolling
on Facebook and I don't know if you've
seen it but there's just constant
articles of like big bold like headlines
of like us confirms to possibly declare
war on China and you're just like what
the [__] like scrolling you're like holy
[__] are we gonna war with China yeah
and it's like no it's just clickbait but
out of all the clickbait like I'm
friends with all these people and
they're friends with me so if they share
it then their friend sees it which I see
it again and now I've seen the same post
thirty times one of them when you begin
to trust it to anyway yes we do this
innately you begin to trust it like [__]
if like thirty people right now just
posted that we're going to war with
China maybe well that's how we've grown
to work we want to make sure that we're
in on what's really going on and it's
part of our how we formed civilizations
like you've got you've got a bunch of
people gathering together in
if you accidentally listen to the cuckoo
guy you're gonna die next year in the
winter but if you listen to the smart
guy who other people are like okay he
seems to know what's going on like that
that's what like you know Trust is it's
it's grown so so let's let's talk about
like let's branch this to truth in this
situation let's let's go so so trying to
think so what we know to be truth so
when we were growing up when we were in
high school do you remember like when
you were reading like history books for
example like I think we're talking
history of is really like the story that
you read let's say this was written in
1940 like originally the rough draft was
written in 1946 for this book that we're
reading in in 2003 right and then it's
like reprinted and then finally it's
released in late 1963 is the final
version and then it's ruin reprinted and
they kind of like retell the same
stories maybe they I don't know how
they'd do this how they make history
books but they tweak it and write we so
what what happened as you well you're a
few years on army so when I was going
through school I was like we were in
high school by the time phones were like
pretty much everybody's got one
in like we still it was like a lot of
people still had to like pay for
internet so you didn't really click on
your internet icon like you accidentally
like you would try to not ever it would
be an accident forensic fuck-ups cost me
ninety eight cents so but but the thing
is so that the difference in our reality
say when I was that age and kids now the
history books and again I haven't been
to high school recently I don't know my
[__] history books say for sure but
the history books were saying this is
how it happened and this person was in
charge in Columbus was this in Lewis
Clark did this and the Indians they
they're totally fine with us being here
we didn't kill any of them and whatever
you know like history books that don't
tell the actual truth like here's what
seriously happened because the person
writing the history book is on the side
that the the narrative is on yeah
they're right a positive narrative right
but the but the thing is like a lot of
our everything was built on that side so
so so the difference the difference
being
how do young kids like trust adults and
trust these things that they're reading
in and ever-changing like like they get
out like you you could be in you know
let's say ninth grade and you're like
your teacher is telling you about what
happened with Columbus and blah blahs
maybe it's the same stuff like as a
smaller older town same stuff that I
learned 10 years ago they haven't
changed it let's say and like the kid
can be like well actually I just looked
on Google and I found like 15,000 people
who actually disagree and they said that
like we actually killed all those
Indians and or you know like whatever
like here's the real story so like I
wonder like what's what's the boiling
point of that sort of thing like truth
like kids aren't going to trust the
older people they're gonna be like I'm
not gonna listen to the way that you're
telling us how to how to run like like
what if we throw it what if younger kids
accidentally throw out baby with the
bathwater because they're like you guys
are just making up so much [__] that's
biased see that you don't see I think I
think the this position that we're in
now is one of the most important
positions that we could be in back then
when you read a history book that was
printed and for 50 years was the premier
history book of all the knowledge in the
u.s. to teach all the kids was that
Christopher Columbus came and shook
hands with the Indians and had a turkey
you know yeah
mobile that sort of thought is now wiped
away because we now know the facts and
skepticism has crept its way in if you
went from a straight one fact one
thought one way mindset to now no maybe
it was actually kind of like this or
maybe it kind of maybe went this way and
they actually slayed all the Indians and
stole all the land you're gonna have
conflict between both sides you're gonna
have people that are strongly supportive
of the old ways and strongly supportive
of the new ways that's where we're at
now we're in a mixing of knowledge of no
this is the way it is and no this is the
way it
could be or could potentially be and I
think with the amount of knowledge that
is being put out right now that is so
untrustworthy or it is just so hard to
believe
I think that's gonna breed people to go
out and be like you know what [__] that
mainstream is not going to put out some
real real news what actually went down
then I will and with that comes a new
breed a new generation of reporters a
new generation of you know people who
are insightful on certain things you
know what I mean like like boxing went
out of style for a while it was a huge
huge thing before UFC came in and and
kind of wiped out boxing and then boxing
was like we kind of got a kind of got to
do something different but at the same
time we got to go go back to our roots
because when he was dying out they were
they were finding out that there were
they were calling fights they were you
know placing bets on fights for
entertainment purposes to maximize
revenue you know they were saying like
we're gonna let blah-blah-blah win this
fight because now we can have him fight
this next guy that'll be a mega fight
and then if he loses to him then he can
rematch the guy that he just lost to
because they did an epic fight and it
was a split decision it was really close
and people caught on to that and they're
like holy [__] like we can't trust that
that's that's it's set up and it looks
set up and it looks fake and so now
they're like jumping back into it and
they're just like alright this is real
boxing this is like we're going to ESPN
now like we're not even doing a
pay-per-view thing like we'll do paper
review for the big fights but ESPN will
show it to the whole world for free
boxing is back you know I think that's
the same thing if that kind of makes
sense with
the information era that we're going
through is we're in the mud right now
but we're gonna crawl out of it and
we're gonna get we're gonna shower off
and we're gonna get super clean and
we're entering a new age of technology
which can lead us into the next
conversation so okay so fill me in with
fill in the listener where I leave in
blank so I'm just gonna quick summary
LAN musk was just a couple years ago and
Joe Rogan essentially he announced
neural Inc which is a microchip in your
brain and well not exactly a microchip
in your brain but essentially this it's
within the next year for one said that
will be the first one in a human skull
they drill a little thing around the
side of your head and they peel back a
little part of your skull there and they
put a little thing in and then it seals
back over it cuz it's kind of like a
cork for your brain and it's like flush
back over that um and what this does is
it I mean what it would even say like
cures it brain diseases cares brain
diseases is what he claims is most
survivors and dementia and you can walk
again if you're a quadriplegic and [__]
like like literally if it's controlled
to your brain you can learn how to read
so what they reactivate yeah so what
they do I'm pretty sure that they use
sound frequencies and I think that it's
the same technology that like Nikola
Tesla like the Tesla coil I think it's
similar like the frequencies not
entirely sure could we talk on my but
somebody proofread me on that Jamie but
Jamie the like it so it's like I don't
know how it determines like okay so you
don't have movement of your right arm
well it knows we know now where the spot
in your brain is that correlates the
movement of your right arm like so you
get in a car wreck and you hit a
specific spot in your brain they're
gonna be like oh yeah that's why your
left elbow feels that you know it's all
connected your whole body is connected
to to your to your brain obviously and
you could see the lack of signals yes
and electrical signals and so it's
supposed to stimulate those yes we're in
supposed to reform them I guess like it
reforms I don't know pathways is it the
correct word cuz that's like neuro
elasticity but man I'd like it's hard to
wrap my head around but essentially
we're going to have like dementia
Alzheimer's like this is stage one so so
if you have so here's an example that
Elon used on the podcast was like it's a
you have seizures and say you're about
to do the thing right before like your
body senses that you're about to have a
seizure like so whatever things that
happened in someone's brain right before
they have a seizure
we now we've studied that we know that
we know what goes on so now we have a
thing the neuro-link that when they put
it it'll sense it'll know as soon as
someone's like they're walking around
they have the normal day they're not any
different but they have their brain just
cancelled out a seizure or something so
like they're walking around and their
body starts to seize or their brain
starts to have that first initial thing
the neuro-link sends a sound frequency
or a frequency and don't quote me on the
sound part that negates it or opposites
it or whatever more informs that
whatever and it turns off the seizure so
like someone's gonna bond yeah yeah like
do this like it's just crazy that
changes like everything in our world
that literally if if he's claiming to
cure multiple multiple chronic diseases
that are responsible for claiming the
lives of so many people you have to be
one of the greatest engineers that this
world has ever seen no I said at one
point you know at one point in time one
device can then negate all the negative
effects of disease and right and that's
just stage one he's just saying that you
know disease and and carrying these
things is the first phase but now we're
going to integrate it into a full brain
implant where you can then use the
access of the Internet via bluetooth and
become a superhuman cyborg decide early
yeah and so in his argument now is that
you are already a cyborg which I can't
disagree with abso
I cannot disagree with him listener if
you have a cell phone you're a cyborg
you don't leave the house without idea
it's not physically attached to you I
mean Oh unless you have an iPhone why
wait basically it is physically attached
to you because
if it's above 50% which it highly is
above 50% of people having a cell phone
in their pocket at all times
mm-hmm you're a cyborg you all your
information your life information is put
into this device mm-hmm the music you
like it pictures that you have
throughout like you're storing your
physical memories into this thing you
are physical memories that's an interest
is a cool memory it's not something
that's like real that's like a new thing
we have known with pictures physical
memory physical all the time
memories and short-term it blows my mind
that you can capture life like snapchat
in short-term send it real-time and your
friends across the [__] globe can
open it up and see what you just sent
mm-hmm like real real-time right that's
so crazy
and if you don't think that that that's
that's kind of straying off I just
wanted to say I think it is so crazy
that people that think that you know
that the meditative woowoo like 10-4 Hat
sort of kind of people are crazy and
like you know they think they're weird
tree huggers they're like they think
things are connected you send little
words in a text and hit okay and hope
that through the [__] right weird how
does he give your [__] do that
ether where that your friend is going to
get this message
yeah it really ether and if it doesn't
happen immediately now you're so pissed
through the university but ether yeah
through nothingness like you can just
receive [__] and like send it and you
can like your location can be
act from a satellite in space like dude
like just think about like the
impossible has been created mm-hmm that
seems impossible well dude to me it
seems like it's like at what point do we
allow it to change as much as it does at
what point do we make society match up
and become UFC rather than WWE well at
what point do we and not just political
system but like so like it's hard like
fully grasp like so think of like the
nature of the self let's say like like
you can like learn about these things
like oh okay like what
oh I'm not like a person riding around
behind my eyes like what do you mean
like where is like Who am I like I was I
was saying earlier the example like what
what's your ego right what the ego
started when let's say where the thing
after monkeys where in evolution we came
after monkeys however the [__] that
happened put a aliens alien suit sound
convinced dude I think that it's I think
that it was a drug-sniffing photos
mushrooms I think we started technically
eating mushrooms and it changed our
consciousness is stoned ape theory yeah
yeah I love it I think that's kind of
where I'm at right now but um so anyway
so so at one point when we start getting
smarter we start using language because
say say you're a monkey and you're
trying to communicate with the other
monkey across room you have a banana and
you're trying to tell them well then
you're pointing at it or you're you know
you're shaking it whatever it like
you're trying to signify this is the
thing I'm talking about it's a thing so
you created a thing to make civilization
and like make a community like advance
the evolution of consciousness really
so you started naming things you picked
up a banana Oh banana and that noise you
make with your mouth means banana in you
and you pick up a pointy rock and that's
what you used to kill fish and you and
you call that rock rock and so the
person across from you the monkey
crossed me goes rock well and you nod or
whatever and he knows that that thing
sounds like a good song right right yeah
yeah so so eventually once you start
naming things right you have to you get
to a point where you're pointing at a
fat banana rock and then you point
monkey across from you and you're like
what are you what are you and so you
have a name and you're Jeff Jeff Jeff
and from there Jeff here monkey Jeff you
monkey from there you you know so that's
so that's how like if you think of like
what's the ego what's the like who do we
think we are so so rewinding back in
time from what I was saying but so at
what point do we actually start
accepting that because like so so like
that fact right that that's something
that a lot of people can't comprehend
that's a little something that is
probably seen as false or something that
doesn't you know I'm click to a lot of a
lot of ways of thinking the way that we
run the world is as if that is untrue
that's what that's what I'm getting out
the way that we currently run the world
the way that we do like the like Donald
Trump ego for example like he's he's the
best example of like how an ego mind who
doesn't realize that he's not existing
behind his eyes he's not a person riding
around in his brain a body like of him
running the world so like at one point
in civilization in society do we start
living as if we're not like we can't not
have an ego I suppose but I think with
the amount of comfortability that we're
feeling is making the physical okay
right now we live in a physical world
like that everything is physical if you
say Donald Trump you're gonna think of
like his wispy ass hair is blonde hairs
wrinkly face even image that pops up and
yeah you have an image of who he is and
not a feeling of what he possesses or
like Edie you know what I mean it's I
just think it's so crazy that people
can't see people for who they are and
and most people would be like you know
what no like I see them for who they are
but realistically like if you cut off my
arm
I would then not have an arm it is just
an attachment of myself of this body
that I'm trapped
like it belongs to you because your
piece to it but it's separated from you
it's it's if you cut it off I no longer
have it but I'm still alive it's still
me like like wit where are you yeah so
you're not fit you're not physical
you're not because if you were you you
probably a piece of you would be with
your arm and maybe it is I don't know
but like maybe it is I don't know but
like you can lose an arm and still be
you you know and you can lose your legs
and your other arm and both your ears
and your nose and your lips and [__] and
like you're still you I think we're
gonna get to a point in life where if
this neural ink really goes to that
level which I believe it will because
technology is just advancing to a point
where humans don't even ask what they
want from life they just accept what the
new technology is with open arms we're
just a ball habits is all we are
yeah hobbits that we're trained by
somebody that's not that didn't
knowingly look out for our best interest
at the beginning and I think that with
knowledge that's what stuff is with
knowledge comes a lack of emotion if you
ever met a scientist if you ever met a
astrophysicist or something like that a
lot of their talks a lot of their ideas
come with not a person behind them there
they come with knowledge behind them and
an idea and you have to separate the
self from the idea because if you get
consumed in the idea and you make it
personal then things kind of go wacko
conversation relax yeah and and you
can't like like if somebody rejects your
idea for this scientific finding or
whatever the case may be you can't have
your identity attached to that idea
right and I think that's where knowledge
is is like a lack of identity and I
think if we keep pursuing that then we
will become like this identity this
species of like what people
keep saying it's like the aliens of like
a big head in small body cuz we don't
need to beat each other up and let
everyone know who's a big dog in the
yard we're all just like mega smart and
like don't need room for sex because we
don't feel any urge to like physically
we express ourselves from our biological
a were lower consciousness yelling we're
heading towards that direction or going
that way and right it's well so do you
and believe in do what do you think
about the singularity do you know if you
are that singularity I've heard it I'm
not I'm not super keen on it either
I think it's essentially what the
thought is is like the final one human
consciousness and it's like this weird
thing I think that it's I believe some
religions like like don't like it I
think that it's like a bad thing but um
but but I think that it's a
misunderstood thing more than thing so
so my opinion is that whatever we will
be considering what we will end up
calling the same Larry I think is
happening within our lifetime for sure
but just like I think it's gonna be like
within within like five years so
branching to how quickly time and how
quickly things move now so like neural
link is gonna be within a year I think
so think about how how much [__] that
speeds up like we're going to we're not
just going to have this wonderful uh
technology and then like people who are
poor are still gonna have to like go
through the shitty chemotherapy virgins
you know like the it's the best we have
while we're trying to figure out the
cure for this thing that you're
suffering through you know the like the
shitty prescription drugs that people
are just like that are destroying their
like physical bodies like hurting their
you know liver and kidneys and and those
sort of things what is the the future
with neural link existing so like I say
we're having this podcast and we know
there's 700 people there are 700 people
who have neural link and it [__]
works like at what rate art is our
entire civilization like yo you know it
could fix
grandma like she can literally remember
us it's like a kid dude it's Steve could
walk again like holy [__] he's been in
wheelchairs in Tallaght so-and-so oh it
could literally give you vision back if
your corneas have like like like
deprecated what you saying like they
like if you need to it will rebuild your
corneas if you don't see like holy [__]
and that's technology without any yet I
think it changes a lot it's uh I think
it's it's a lot different than what
people assume it to be as far as like
the fact of the whole world getting it
everything it's uh it's kind of it's
gonna be like Tesla you know the the
cars are expensive not the average
consumer can buy them they're amazing
for the world they are the first
electric car there's luxury that is
[__] from the future if you ever
ridden in one it is the coolest driving
car I've ever been in it is the fastest
car I've ever won dude they're so cool
they're beautiful they're amazing
they're out of our reach they're out of
the everyday person's reach and I think
that's what's gonna happen with an ER
link at least the first stages are gonna
be like you gotta have some money to to
have any of these effects happen to you
at first and then you know once the
watch record them oh sorry
I'm good broad going to cut off any yak
you go once the newer updates come out
and the newer models come out and things
like that I think they'll be like passed
down like an old iPhone you know ya know
you got the one brother din accuse your
Alzheimer's would have [__] up your
left leg we don't we haven't figured out
I got a wimp it's just rest of your life
- beta switch have you seen the movie
Elysium I was just about to think about
that is that the is that the movie with
that name Matt Damon has their plug in
the back of it yeah that's the one
that's literally what I was there today
and I were talking about that it's it's
a man in a fantasy world it's like wow
that's crazy but it's like oh [__] so so
that's kind of what I was pointing and I
think is is this this gap that's going
to be created very quickly between the
very rich
in the very poor I mean Elon Musk is the
kind of guy who is not stupid and he's
aware of those sort of things so he's
going to do the cost of materials to
create this sort of thing it's gone so
so it's it's so much smaller it's less
material like so massively producing
these things like I'm hoping that we can
have the amount of time let's say that
the people on the ground like in the
movie Elysium mm-hmm there's gonna be
some sort of like there's hella people
with knurling covers help people with
these magical whatever [__] is
scientific curing their disease they're
living up in the sky though because
they're the rich glass there's gonna be
a huge gap between the really poor and
the really rich is what I'm getting yeah
yeah I'm hoping that people like Elon
seems like he has like a good you know
my intuition tells me that I don't know
it seems like he's going to try to
lessen that gap the amount of years that
there is a huge gap I hope that it's you
know four to five years and it's like
okay yeah there we were struggling for a
couple years and there was a lot of
people who were like literally still
dying from diseases that people are
walking around cured from but I'm hoping
there's yes time do you believe in do
you believe in ur link as or the
progression of technology as a way in
which humanity should go and should
progress to without hesitation or
without sort of that because you're a
very very spiritually enlightened person
you are connected to the earth you
meditate every day outside you you know
you are very consciously aware of
people's emotions and feelings are you
nervous that this could be an avenue
that takes the human out of a being I'm
not nervous about it but I think that's
what's happening well so and are you on
board for that
weirdly we really kind of but not like
because that's what I want
like I just I just think that logically
so if you see us as organic bootloaders
I think even Elon has been I think he's
the one who said that like if you see
humanity as
Organic bootloaders like we're always
just trying to progress like have you
studied Graham Hancock do you know
Graham Hancock oh I've heard of his name
so he is essentially someone who has
been trying to prove like mainstream
media for lack of a better term there
that like he's like studied the pyramids
and like how time worked and how the ice
age really worked and he's like hey
there's a cycle that happens every stone
so million years and it's going to
happen soon and we need to [__] get
the [__] off the planet something I
don't know if I don't know if he
believes we should got the planet but
essentially he points out that we
haven't thought long-term about our
history like we had we don't fully
understand history and I think how do I
runs out I don't want to put ideas I
don't want to misspeak on what leads him
but so so check his stuff out he's just
kind of like revitalized it's like what
actually happened in history like some
of his some of his ideas are pretty
far-fetched I'm not saying that I
believe every single one but he's got a
lot of great info so but so might a lot
of my connections are I think that if
you detach like I was saying like a live
in a world where we don't have ego at
the minds where we don't have we're not
attached to the the life that we have
because we know that it ends we enjoy
every second because we know that in
some amount of years maybe right away
maybe instantly maybe in 15 years we're
going to die so we live a society that
doesn't accept death we tried to paint a
story as in there's a magical better
life in this after death or we just kind
of ignore it we kind of just try to
maximize right now it's on the other
side yeah and so but but if so say we
weren't doing that right say we like if
you just look at if you take the the
personification of humanity I guess as a
weird thing to say out of the equation
and you look at like what is the earth
doing what's happening what what is it
like if you didn't know what it was but
you all you had was you're sitting in
space with a notepad and you're like
studying it for billions and billions of
years and you're just looking at the
earth and this might be naive I don't
know you you're like what is this
[__] doing eventually it's like okay
it's turning it green
and it started and then all sudden you
know you see what like flowers or you
start seeing different things pop up and
like what used to be one big landmass
one big chunk over the billions of years
it starts to do different things and it
formulates an atmosphere and it starts
to pop up like the fish somehow get legs
and they can walk out you know the
evolution like if you're watching
evolution on the earth happen if we take
ourselves out of like ourself like
Brendan and Jake out of it and I'm just
observing what the earth is doing
without inserting myself as a human on
it it seems like Earth is doing this
thing like it's like like its opening
its peacock wings but then like it's
peacock wings may only stay open for you
know a few hundred years and then it
withers back and completely dies and
burst into flame in in life and in
recreation and [__] just restarts right
so I think if you think I think because
if you look at what consciousness is
doing to humans as just a being like
there's no other we assume that there's
no other like animal that really has a
consciousness that thinks as advanced as
us or as like because there's no other
animals that are like we need to leave
the atmosphere and like why is that a
thought or have like what is what is
consciousness trying to communicate
through humanity rather than
consciousness is humanity if you just
think of what is consciousness trying to
say through humanity because humanity is
the highest level it's separate entity
yeah and if you if it's so the way that
I see and this is where it loops back to
your question Brandon is is is
consciousness being okay if you think of
consciousness as just the earth like cut
like Gaia like like the earth and life
it is itself what we know to be alive it
is we are that and it wants life we know
that consciousness earth wants to live
because that's what it's always been
doing it's creating different species
and it's creating different animals and
it's always life like a gazelle hides
from a lion because it doesn't want to
die is favored as life
and we have them like again if you like
speed up time when you're observing the
earth do this it looks like it's like
they slowed down like the gazelle and
the lion but if you just speed it up
it's just this quick little dot on the
on the earth that's just doing its thing
yeah so if we look at like what are
humans doing and what's the thing that
they're doing I think that humans might
actually be trying to get off earth
because earth might be doing another
like withering thing soon you so I think
that we are consciousness but for some
reason in a sack of meat if I'm right
we're trapped in sack of me and I'm not
I don't know how a hundred percent
confirmed I feel them is kind of
observing this now as we're talking
about a bit but a if if we see if we see
ourselves as not just the universe
consciousness but where earth the planet
particular like Whitley cuz there's some
crazy connection to that itself you look
at us as like where the earth is just
one of those little did the wishy
flowers those dandelion was she flowers
and like it's gonna blow eventually like
it's some force some something is gonna
blow on that earth and the little seeds
hopefully sprout out throughout the
universe and plant more little seeds of
earth throughout because that can be
able to withstand right because they
have new knowledge yeah you in buy seeds
on other Earth's I mean like let's say
us going to Mars
so we now that we're on Mars we have the
entire consciousness the entire
knowledge of an entire Earth lifetime
like because we not only have our
hundred years that were on the Reno 60
or whatever the [__] it is we have all
the knowledge that all the other humans
have told us in like books and an
informational in the internet yeah so so
you have if you think of consciousness
as the entity that started on earth as
far as we know started you know probably
big bang bang is probably more specific
I don't I just don't know but but if you
think of us as the earth yeah I think
we're where the Alan Watts says if you
observe the earth we thought it wasn't
doing anything it was just rocks he's
like but but no wait on second thought
it's it's peopling it's peopling he sees
he says that and I was like oh that I
kind of make sense you know and and what
are the we take we take responsibility
for the peopling but we're just the
consciousness riding around in the
peopling and I think that if we detach
ourselves from that and it sounds like
gripping emotions and humanity out from
what it may actually be but it's it
sounds dis sensitive to humanity almost
in a way in to think of us as just a
consciousness that needs to escape earth
but I think we might be like we're not
kind of on a path of killing ourselves
for one yeah but yeah it's it's just
kind of fighting super-crazy thought
what if from the beginning you say that
it is highly plausible that we came from
apes that took the idea is that eight
took psychedelic mushrooms or
psychedelic substances they were just
like enhance technically yeah enhance
their cognition and created abstract
thought and things like that but for
anyone who has taken mushrooms DMT or
some sort of psychedelic you understand
that you're faced with separate entities
or conscious thought that seems beyond
you that speaks to you in a way that is
extremely profound in a way that you've
never thought before it's like it's a
higher than experiences playlist it's
which you should because you would just
be like whoa I mean I'm taking a lot of
random drug I mean one time I think I
did LSD but it was just a different
night we had gone going on but yeah so
what I was thinking is maybe there is a
certain consciousness that says this is
super high talk but there's a certain
consciousness that the earth has within
itself or the universe has within itself
that is embedded into the earth could be
in mushrooms or whatever
then used animals like monkeys as a host
and began to coincide and coexist and
use that back and forth psychedelic
enhancement mmm and with a combination
of evolving species and now we've gotten
so deep into it that you can tell that
we are a weird combination of this human
thought and human I don't know that this
different this definitely deeper level
of structural thinking and abstract
thought and creativeness and also we
have this very very animalistic
we're always wanting what's best for our
survive our immediate survival not
necessarily someone else's to the point
where it tricks us so we don't even
realize it that we're doing it exactly
it's an equal mine it's an urge and when
you are faced with someone who is very
enlightened with themselves and
understands that there's this you need
to wake up to this separation of your
animalistic self and your conscious self
you know of
you know I don't know if you've felt it
which I feel like you have oh yeah I
mean I told you how obviously by the way
you live and by the way you think and
articulate yourself there's two sides of
you there is a very animalistic side and
there's a very conscious side and there
is a body of you that just is innately
you that you just kind of live your day
to day life like but there's a clear
divide between the two and I
it feels like a host situation to me
kind of because it's a shark doesn't
necessarily know a lot of the times that
it has like those little things swimming
on its side and it's it's you know that
little creatures like eating off all the
bacteria or all the bugs that could be
harmful to the shark and you know behind
him but he's never looking behind him
he's always looking in front of them for
the things that's going to ensure his
survival you have to look backwards at
yourself and be like what is or what is
me what is helping me what is harming me
what is I mean what and then what am i
what's going on what's going on here
yeah and not just like I'm here to live
and eat and sleep and [__] he says who
knows who why you know what I mean like
like it's it's it's interesting that
there's you know well what okay so what
do you I think we should stay in this
direction
I don't think of it I'm like this drives
neural ink so what what is okay okay so
going back to neural ink in what it
changes in our day-to-day like like
obviously the in this the thing with new
technology is in our heads what kind of
thing like oh it's out and then all of a
sudden in an instant everything every
how's it and we can get it like it's not
like that who's gonna be a trickle down
but but we are it it's such a time where
this [__] is so fast it's so fast like
it's unbelievably fast right in in in so
I'm just curious I just think like the
the gap between I don't want to keep
defaulting that but like the gap between
the people who like I mean because
because there's a lot of people and I'm
not saying there's anything not a damn
thing wrong with them there's people who
don't like they're just in Alaska living
they have no TV and they don't know what
the [__] going on they don't they're
just living you know I mean like they're
just you know and I could
yeah that's just their way life right so
so how do we how is the world going to
coincide because right now we have this
weird world where people where people
are arguing and killing each other over
presumptions they have of each other
that aren't actually true how do we have
a world where it's not presumptuous
there is your 85 year old grandpa Billy
is literally talking to a [__] cyborg
that's 17 years old like he's delivering
his package and in my cyborg I mean of
17 year old boy with microchips in his
brain with with silicone data in his
brain that is you know that I mean
cybernetically connected to the cloud
right of data that is this hive mindset
of everyone's collected information into
one odd conscious subconscious not
conscious thing just it's just knowledge
it's just knowledge that's it it's
nothing else you know all right it's
it's something that you can just tap
into yeah like what is it's just really
hard to to envision the gap between here
and there right it is but it it still
blows my mind to this day that the
knowledge that we already know the
simple facts about history and things
like that that are known how to do
finances how to file your taxes like you
have to go to school for that and a lot
of people get ripped off on becoming a
doctor when most people know like like
there are doctors out there and there
are people that know how to teach what
goes on in the human body and yet
they're charging people's life's work of
mm-hmm
everything they earned in debt onto this
person for information that is already
known by people
it's right yeah it's free knowledge is
free knowledge is absolutely free it's
it's me saying hey the sky is blue and
you go the sky's blue the sky is blue
mm-hmm holy [__] the sky is blue
that's knowledge right there right if I
told you this this beer bottle was
transparent or translucent or whatever
it is says and you're like what's
translucent no you could see straight
through it right oh it's transparent
that's that's what it is yeah that's
what it is
oh I didn't know that now I do that's
what that's what college is and that's
what people are paying their entire
life's work for well so even before that
before college I mean I talked about
kind of the breakdown of communities on
an individual level think about and this
is kind of a storybook fairy tale sort
of version in a movie hallmark situation
but you know you're like gosh I'm making
these cookies and I've been living on my
own for two years now I can't remember
so I'm gonna call grandma and grandma
how long do I put these good I set the
oven to but she's gonna tell you exactly
and whatever but like nowadays I mean
just cooking some cookies you're like
I'm gonna look on Google because it
literally takes five seconds compared to
calling grandma and eating that I mean
like so although so imagine that
situation where everything is just
simplified like we're just cutting out
other people everything is simplified
and where we are kind of like taking the
situation and amplifying it in every way
like information like we're kind of
losing the need to interact with each
other because all your questions all
your wonder which is what makes us want
to walk up to each other and wonder what
that person is about oh they're not
going to hurt me like what's happening
here I think but you you you alleviate
the need for like communication I guess
oddly it obviously is probably a
conspiracy at the highest level but
right
it seems so weird that we are in a time
like this where technology already
forces people to look down at their
phone if they're sitting and standing in
line at the DMV or whatever and just
waiting they don't interact with other
people there they're secluded - what
makes them comfortable they phone
themselves and they're like I don't want
to talk excuse me I don't want to talk
to anyone now you throw an
infectious-disease in there and you have
people like I was saying before covering
up their mouths so you can't see any
facial expressions from people you're
taught to stay at a distance lock
yourself inside for however long we've
been locked inside for on hours and
hours and hours and hours and hours and
days and and it seems like they're
trying to integrate a life in which
people are becoming like that will be
the norm of like being secluded being by
yourself and having everything gifted to
you is going to be enough for life and
to take it even further as we go and
divulge into technology and new things
and ways of life like technology is so
so nuts because we see life as like if
you were to think of dimensions near
like well you can go twelve dimensions
deep like if you were this and make a
guru or whatever and then you have the
maker of Microsoft saying I can plug you
into 36 different dimensions the VR
headset that has all sensory sound touch
like you won't even know you could I
could tell you that I'll give you a
lifetime
worth a gladiator warrior's life you'll
know the feelings you'll know the pain
you'll die you'll wake up and it'll only
be two minutes of your life ten minutes
of your life ten hours of your life
whatever the case may be
and you're gonna wake up and be like
what the [__] I just lived my whole
[__] life oh I lost my kids oh no you
were just playing a game
chill out remember hey Brandon remember
watch something what are the odds that's
not exactly what's happening right now
it could be you know what I mean - like
that is the direction we're moving in
you know it's like from Rick and Morty
[__] it's some Rio is exact real real
possibility of like coming and people
don't understand like they're still
stuck in this physical world and live I
think that's a little bit more of the
older generation because they don't
really understand it but like they can
literally like my little brother was
telling me he bought a oculus rift hmm
thing there's no room in he said his
Netflix app on there it's like you have
your little joysticks or whatever and
you're looking in that in the headset
and he clicks on Netflix and it takes
him to a secluded lake with a campfire
in front of him and it's crackling ooh
and there's a levitating massive screen
above the lake that is illuminating the
sky and all the trees around him and
it's playing his favorite movie on top
of this lake as he's sitting in front of
or behind a kiss was real he did this is
what oculus does right now this is what
oculus does right now he can watch you
can watch whatever Netflix show above
this floating levitating massive movie
sized screen of floating above a lake
well the stimulus do we so I haven't
done virtually Audia is either of I so
so but I've heard from people they're
like dude no it's real like you like if
you're walking on like an edge like you
like won't go to the edge I get scariest
foot I've known my little sister I've
done a rollercoaster one mm-hmm
and I had [__] you not
I it would it started off taking off
just like a roller coaster and it's all
vr so it's like they could make some
like ungodly drop that's like whoa I'm
we're about to take off and and the
machine simulates like what kind of
Timothy it to end tipping and things
like that so we tip and I literally
slammed my head on the back when we
started falling down cuz it started
tipping and I looked down and I was like
oh [__] we're taking off like down and
it felt like from what the feeling felt
like my stomach dropped my like the
thing leaned forwards on my chair was
forward and I hit my head in the back
because I was trying to lean back and it
was so real it was so real and the wind
was blowing in my face
from each direction and it was just and
this is the very very very very
beginning stages of it this is where the
this is like the PlayStation 1 oh yeah
this is the shoe that they're selling to
kids like think about like how advanced
the technology really likely is yeah on
the level of the government or military
is funding a lot of this [__] for
whatever reason like training example
holy [__] they already have they've
already released no dad training sorry
to cut you off again no no they've
already released that 5g it's not gonna
coronavirus I'm not gonna go into five
grade now they're gonna take my vid for
how fast 5g is they're allowing doctors
with like extremely extremely good
trauma doctors to go via virtually to
connect the some gloves or some sort of
thing to a robot that's in Afghanistan
and work on soldiers that have just been
shot and killed mm-hmm with their hand
movements yeah real-time like the most
minimal lag that you can believe we're
no longer limited by the physical world
no our weakest genius people can be
anywhere they need to be it you can have
you know your your brilliant people
working together in the same room I mean
it's kind of like what Holograms do on
Star Wars right now like
I think that it skyrockets our asses
right into the future like we are just
about to slingshot it we we jumped we
jumped with technology we quantum leap
because I mean just think about it like
from what is it like let's say like says
1600 at 1900 what happened what what
massive technologies like really just
took over though then one was like
electricity and late 1800s Early 1900s I
think because after that then that's
what the car started you know taking
into effect and things like that but
just even for that example of like like
even if some some amazing things did
happen like it took hundreds of years
for some amazing things to happen people
were still like raping and killing and
pillaging and hitting he's in [__]
believes and and using sword for people
ago there was slaves and [__] three
people ago and now we're moving a
hundred years in the span of three years
or four years five years right could you
like if you look at an iPhone eight now
you're like that's a piece of [__] piece
of [__] my got my own fine you shake it
out yeah get out of here my whole screen
my whole screen is filled you know what
I mean like it's all I could touch it
all mm-hmm now they have foldable phones
and now they have all this stuff like
well so our perception changes because
even just the phone like I was talking
about how like at the very beginning I
was mentioning how like on the 14th of
March it was like were chill I think
it's fine and then 16th March is like
get the [__] in the house don't touch
anybody like salt drink bleach like the
fast technologies the thinking about
phones I actually had a time because I
had like um when I was younger I rented
a room from like a kind of a hoarder
situation and so just really like germs
and in touching people and touching
things that I didn't like like very much
like affected my like mental cognitive
ability so
OCD kind of so like touching your screen
like if you had a phone that you weren't
supposed to touch the screen it's just a
button phone mm-hmm it stresses me out
when people touch their screens my tie
Lee Daniels could actually account for
this mood always [__] with me
so like flip phone and someone puts
their bare finger on the screen this
seems so weird right like why would that
bother you but I'm telling you back then
the only time you would see a screen
like this before phones was like a TV
and is like dude don't [__] put your
screen and don't put your fingers prints
on my screen you don't touch TV screens
and you don't touch like like I don't
like you know finger prints on glass
tables so that's one thing so but what
I'm saying is is that there was a point
where like my perception of reality like
you know maybe I was just young and in
high school sort of thing but our our
perception of like what we feel about
these objects what we feel about these
this technology changes like even
internally like it changes like my our
physiology like I would get stressed out
when say you know you touch a screen but
now it's like you you Tut you only touch
the screen there's no buttons on my
phone like so I changed I I developed
into it because I'm like I want this
technology so bad I forget exactly what
I was trying to point a finger out there
but if we look at I guess just our
adaptation and our ability to change
like it seems like it's like even our
personality in our like acceptance of
these technologies may may change very
quickly
like when front phones first came out
I'm sure there was tons of people
internet first came out but like it's
crazy like I'm not using that that's
stupid and then five years later they're
completely different person they're on
Facebook every day they're they're using
the internet every day like we we see
our advancement in technology from where
we're at at the moment we discover it
but we don't realize how quickly like oh
shoot it's only been a year and a half
and I literally hated that technology a
year ago like we don't we don't look
back and realize that we that we were
kind of against certain technologies in
certain ways like before it's you know
not too late but as before it's where it
were consumed by it so like I know at
one point we're gonna be in virtual
reality but also just before we go into
virtual reality
it's a it's a it's slimy the way they do
it it's very very consciously slime
slime it's very very slimy it's kind of
like commercials for movies or
commercials for for products and things
like that it's an innate thing it's that
you don't necessarily know you even
realize your phone will slow down it's
making you think that your CPU a
processor or anything like that in your
phone is is slowing down you start to
lose service you apps are kind of
sketchy a little bit as your phone gets
older you're going to realize that it
boots on a little bit slower it's it's
gonna drop calls a little bit more all
these things happen innately
because they want you to upgrade your
phone you know they make it hard for you
to have this phone hmm so even if you
fight it and you're like you know what
god damn it like I really don't want I
don't want them to stick it to me like I
want to be in control of my phone
situation mm-hmm they're just gonna keep
it's an automated system it's automating
it's it's there's no human behind it
coin god damn it this guy is [__] he
won't give up he won't give up it's a
room 3 it's a robot going give up today
give up does not care give up the next
stashing does what it's programmed to do
I will have you and it's just like it's
a relentless soulless thing that can
that is propelling you to to abide by
the rules that you know coincides with
everybody it's and it's something that
you don't even know happens like or even
if you do know happens you're just like
I'm not bigger than this
company right you know like I just need
my phone right now man I just moved my
phone so how do we unless we state just
so we can continue with trying to let's
say figure out what's going on how is it
if we if we're to assume to continue
moving forward with with pointing out
that yes it's slimy that that's
happening but we're also as a society as
a human race we are slaves to
advancement so the reason why your
iPhone 3 lags is because all the servers
and all the money and all the focus from
Apple has been moved to the next
whatever in the more that you move it
like you know it's kind of like the
newest Xbox has a way more people
working on it them the first Xbox that
ever came out like at some point they're
like hey guys we're gonna shut down
these servers because there's like not
we just don't have a lot of people to
employ it's not returning profit on the
Xbox the old Xbox is so we're gonna shut
it down there's not be able to you know
whatever like so those sort of things
happen like we're a slave to just
[__] momentum of like because it's
not that they don't realize that they're
stepping on people or anything but like
these big technology companies like are
almost there almost a slave to this like
constant like we're talking about with
the inability to be uncomfortable the
inability to be like this is okay where
it's at like it will stumble into what's
next it's a constant like better better
how do we make it better and how do we
make it better than then Microsoft and
faster and faster and how do we make it
better like so our market our market
mind for the human race has kind of like
led to the to the speeding up of
wonderful technologies but at the same
time it's like our detriment it's it's
it's a it's come full circle I in a
sense because these companies have
created a piece of technology that for
some may dislike but for the vast
majority of it when they say that
they're going to create something new
and then the people are like yes yes we
want it we want it we want it you give
it to them
they have it for awhile they know that
new technologies
progressing extremely fast and know that
they get tired of the same old stuff the
people then go back to the to the
company and say well what else you got
and they're like [__] I'll show you what
I got
let's go boys let's go slave to the
consumer yeah and you're now their slave
the consumer because they can't stop
producing for the consumer and it's
making their money so they're like
there's no reason why we should stop
like we're just gonna keep these profits
going and going and the people are
keeping it going so it's like this
never-ending cycle of the people
consuming and the consumers consuming
what people want to consume and just
yeah we're trying to get somewhere where
we're constantly trying to arrive at
somewhere that doesn't exist we're
trying to arrive at so that at the
finish line that never existed kind of
like I was talking about Alan Watts the
dance is not for me to get from the side
of the room to that side of the room
it's about the dance in between so like
are we do you think maybe we're we're a
bit blinded by like thinking we need to
advance I think I think life would be a
little bit better if we knew what
exactly we were advancing for into if
there was a goal if there was a common
goal with the entire world with the
United States with whoever saying by the
year 2040 as a society we want to be
here mmm is this why that is yeah is
this what we're moving forward this what
we want for our people right yes or no
if it's yes let's go [__] full-on and
dress team and you know what yeah like
I'm like I'm gonna work overtime we're
all working as a people right now the
entire world the entire community our
entire country is focused on getting
here by 2040 if we beat that that uh
achievement we've just achieved it if we
come short we still got life to live
we're still we can still get there 24
can we given up on
on accomplishments we've given up on
understanding that there are marathons
to run and all you want to do is just
jog all day you know it's it's just
you're taking the life out of people
when you could approach it differently
you could approach life so much
differently by setting a goal for the
people and not just having them jog in a
circle and make them lifeless and just
make them hate their [__] existence
like you can't have what you want as the
people up top you just have to set it a
goal in a way that resonates with
everyone right I mean so so setting a
goal that resonates with everyone so
like what if we had earlier we are
talking about you mentioned we're having
a nice conversation about Mikan vision
about like you're like I'm asking
yourself like what you want out of life
and you're like kind of you're talking
about how like before bed you kind of
like reconnect with that thing I have
some friends who I was just talking with
yesterday texting with him talking about
how like they have their Christians and
they'd like to read the Bible you know
they're once a day they have look at the
pages or whatever it is but you know so
it's so to me what that does that
reconnects them to like the person that
they want to be like that's like it's a
reminder of their their vision because
like so so I have like the I painted
couple days ago what's your vision on
the wall over here add to it no timing I
know I would i but like so so you were
mentioning that so let me bring him back
into there's four so does humanity have
a vision so I think that we unknowingly
have a vision I think that we're working
towards a vision that's [__] messy or
working towards too many different ones
so if we could have some sort of
coinciding as an earth as a planet or
all like dude we're just kind of like
you guys you keep your nationalism like
America is [__] awesome China is
[__] awesome it's be the way you are
ever going to have differences yeah
point the front of your ship though at
this and like what if what if then some
this is some ideal
amazing cool world where like some
millionaire somebody who's just [__]
like Elon Musk somebody who everybody
loves just says like Earth's vision is
and it's like some great sense in every
second damn you know what if we did just
follow that it does displace a new law
this could go in the place of like you
know law of gravity like you know we
have absolutes in our universe maybe
we're on the brink this is an
interesting concept of thought
experiment we're on the brink of a new
law of discovery so like what goes up
must come down
yeah what every action has an equal
opposite reaction like Einstein's theory
of gravity like all these things
what if we're on the brink of something
that that will be seen as like a
combination of not only consciousness
biological laws but biology laws of the
universe our five senses how we perceive
reality but also it has to do with
society and civilizations because we
can't deny our physical reality like as
much as we are not humans riding around
in like a little controller system in
the back of our brains where we can't
deny that we have like I am also Jake
and you are also Brandon right we have
physical beings and we have through
civilization as how we interpret things
so I'm almost wondering if we're on the
brink as humanity of a new law that's
going to be in the form of poetic
language poetic thematic creativity so
like what is your vision like so you
know people like I I my vision is to end
suffering or my business to see or
experience you know okay so so let's
let's go back and forth what what do you
think what would be a humanity vision I
think first that humanity vision would
be to understand that humanity shouldn't
work for people at the top
have visions just like Elon Musk wants
to go to the moon or just like you know
whatever something like that like mmm
people in power have positions that they
want they have visions that they want to
achieve but they understand that people
are erratic and sporadic and they're
kind of hard to control so let's kind of
mass manipulate them and let's kind of
keep them working around the clock and
things like that so they don't they
don't have the time not only the time to
figure out what we're doing but they
don't have the time to necessarily care
either
they're working so much and they're
worried about how they're gonna keep
food on the table how the bills are
gonna be paid there's that you know
that's all gonna happen but they're kind
of dumb because people work the best
together like no one person is the
smartest one person if you have a
hundred people and it out matches that
one person immediately transfer I ain't
born with nobody around we're already so
close America is a great a great country
that has a lot of free enterprise and
things like that but a lot of it from so
many like almost everyone I know is not
free in a sense of the way they work and
a lot of it is by choice but a lot of it
is because the fear of not being able to
provide for their family there is a way
in which the top government officials
high high ranking business can
understand that let's have a vision but
we've kind of been on the wrong path we
should all kind of work together right
now and figure out if we can get to this
vision faster if we all work together
and all kind of get away from whatever
we're don't need to be working on
because if there's if there's a job
where someone is cleaning baseboards and
a [__] batting cage area and he
doesn't need that job it's a
non-essential job like the boss is just
a dick because he loves clean baseboards
you could be utilizing that human in
another job hmm that is beneficial for
the entire human race that with their
contribution can help us get here and
once we get here we won't need all these
other jobs that that kind of suppress
people and keep them away from their
families and keep them working their ass
off nine-to-five working double jobs not
being able to see their kids until the
weekend whatever the case may be right
we have to come together as a human
species and learn that together is where
we need to go together is the vision
that's the first vision that we need is
absolute together this that's so obvious
right that's nothing you're the most
obvious but it's it's the last you know
we are one like duh yeah let's see on
the podcast we are one we are know that
does it makes complete sense it's like
wire zombie horde so effective cuz they
fight as one you know it's it's also
crazy but like they are so [__]
unstoppable because well they have one
home at you with one common goal and
that is to eat your brains so what is
our our common goal now is I mean it
survive but it's also like as like
there's a comfort appeal to it and how's
this if this fall's comforted though
because they they present comfort with
materialism right and they don't say hey
let's work our ass off as a as United
States people let's work our ass off to
get to this goal along those were along
the way every day you work we're gonna
have
some break time where like everyone
everywhere takes a break we all mingle
we all hmm make sure we're eating
healthy we're all make sure we're
drinking water we all make sure that we
are fulfilling our human needs not just
slave laboring our way up to this goal
that we need to fulfill you know it's
like we're consciously aware that you
are a person you are a person this is
probably a dream world that will never
happen but this is what needs to happen
this is what is very very plausible this
is not it's not something that you can
be like oh no that's that's way out of
the picture there was a statistic that
said that out of most nine-to-five jobs
I think for hours total of like absolute
productivity goes into a job and the
rest of the hours are spent on your
phone working or like like daydreaming
sleeping whatever the case may be
there's so many unutilized hours that
are unnecessary for people that could be
fulfilled in other ways like you could
have group exercises and group meals
like going to Germany is was one of the
nuts experiences for me because they had
they have a beer gardens and so like any
day throughout the day it's always
filled like you know breakfast lunch and
dinner whatever it is like you'll just
be walking around and there's just like
a massive massive massive park or
whatever with park benches everywhere
and people just sit next to each other
and just mingle and they just like talk
and drink beer and have sausage and like
just do whatever and that sort of
community doesn't exist and a lot of
places definitely doesn't exist here I
think just this like slowly integrating
things like that and just so
appreciating like it like knowing where
we're going but appreciating where we
are really because I think we'd get
there faster if we were blatantly honest
about where we want it to go right like
there's you can't even ask ourselves
there's skepticism from the from people
at the top when you lie you're always
thinking of a way to tell the truth
you're always thinking of avenues it's
like chess you tell it you have a lie
that you want to tell someone and if
they try and call your [__] you have
this avenue and if they call you on some
angle from that you have another Avenue
and it's your scapegoat and another one
in another one another one when you tell
the truth and just say hey this is where
we want to go let's talk about this
there might be some negative
repercussions of it but let's talk about
it let's see what like what we got to do
to get here that is kind of cool for
everyone and like beneficial for
everyone it's it just seems crazy that
the obvious is so hard for people to
understand it's so hard for people to
understand that we are destroying the
earth and like [__] millions of cars
throughout the world all day every day
or just driving and just polluting the
world like crazy and you're just like
you know what's the long-term of the way
that we're living life like we don't
like like we detach we're so Instagram
if ocation that we're so caught up in
ourselves that we detached like dude
imagine like but honestly if I was
raising a kid right now I'd be like [__]
man I'm sorry that we're bringing you
like into this world of such unknowns
you know what I mean like like I'm sure
there's plenty of parents who are like
kind of curious like hoping that hoping
that like some sort of clarity comes
yeah man it's like yeah because we like
it dude what's the point of we've got a
half an earth in 100 years we're gonna
have ours and you know we need to be
we're smart enough as a species where we
need to be able to like stop the
momentum and take a look and be like all
right guys like where they're clearly
evolving like the Internet and this
technology like we're clearly changing
like we need to figure out how to help
the rest of the people change and that
sounds like a [__] imperialistic hand
forced neuro-link inside every human
like that's seen that's rough you know
so man it's it's they're astronomical
questions with so much depth and I don't
know how we how we saw them and I think
talking about them just as like like
we're trying to talk about at the level
that we really are like huh I'm no I'm
not genius man I'm no I'm no like
philosopher I'm just I'm just a dude
talk with my friend man I'm just I'm
just contemplating these things that I
study and look up you know I think that
a lot more people should be to I think a
lot more people could make ask
themselves like where am I going but
like I kind of wonder around like
everybody has a hole what are we doing
because you can kind of look at people
with more I don't empathy obviously but
like like if you just see people as how
eyes mm-hmm you know what I mean like oh
like you okay you've you've reacted to
your biological urges the same way that
I have but I know that's not who you are
it's not who that's not who I don't know
it's think it's just a different
perspective of seeing seeing people for
like what they what brings them joy what
like brings the most people some sort of
solidarity and like pureness and
togetherness and light and love and like
because because what are we were just
you know spiritual beings riding around
an Apes body or whatever came after our
name and we're just like trying to
figure it out like we all have none of
us know the [__] answers not a damn
single one a lot of people claim to but
I don't know
do you remember right before you were
born do you remember what you were
thinking about I don't I can't remember
what I was [__] dreaming about last
night as soon as I wake up I forget it
inception right also we ignore dreams
and dreams are we don't ignore dream but
like the average person unless you like
that's a thing you do is study dreams
holy [__] bro eight hours if you 24-hour
day like so much of your time is spent
in a place that you literally don't know
or think about ever you do it you wake
up and you continue doing that you're
doing and someone's like what you dream
about you're like oh it was crazy it was
bah bah and then you move on with your
life and you don't dissect it or like
look
what your subconscious mind is telling
you the craziest craziest craziest [__]
though that happens to so many people is
the feeling of like I remember there was
one time where I was dating this chick
in high school and we had just broken up
and I still like really cared for really
like she was super cool we just didn't
work out whatever like I had a super
super super vivid dream of me driving in
a car with her and we got in a car
accident she died right next to me
damn and I was like I looked over and
she was like dead and I felt what it
felt like to lose her and when I woke up
I literally felt like that agony and I
was like crying and I was like what da
[__] like I was a dream right like I
feel like I I literally felt that and
everything felt real like you couldn't
tell me that wasn't real because in my
head it like was clear as day yeah and I
think it's weird too
like what like what was that trying to
say to you Mike it like it's like like
it is it was it trying to say something
like why did that specific one stand out
to you like why wasn't that another one
of the millions of dreams that you
forget every night right yeah like it's
so interesting and I mean I bet you
there's people that have studied it and
probably actually know quite a bit about
dreams yes I just which would be such a
cool podcast if you had someone on there
[__] listener if you study dreams please
email me at a junkyard love Jake at
gmail.com yes please cuz I am I'm gonna
I'm gonna be sitting right over there
just like staring at ya dreamin yeah
have you ever experienced or tried or
any of that lucid dreaming eye or sleep
paralysis we could talk about - I've
done I've had only one instance of sleep
paralysis lucid dreaming I've not
not really too fond of it dreams within
dreams ish well deep dreaming well lucid
dreaming is as you're dreaming like your
regular night you you are able to awaken
from the dream as in you notice that
you're dreaming and then you kind of
have actually some sort of free will is
a strange word to use in the situation
but you have some sort of allocation to
what you can do you can be like oh okay
likes like some people literally like
like study or like go like like if they
do what they want like I think it's
still kind of like a fantasy side of
your brain my people fly around yeah
yeah you're able to control so you
literally notice that you're in a dream
so what people to do so like I lightly
look into it I'm not like in depth into
it and I haven't done it yet but I do
kind of some of the things like so
there's a thing called a reality check
which sounds sometimes but it's
essentially like as you're going about
your day like if you think about it pops
in your mind just like look at your hand
if you like is this reality yep it's
reality like in in that sounds strange
right but but what happens is is you do
that enough your subconscious starts
formulating these things and then when
you really ask yourself not just like a
habitual thing but you're like [__] like
a literally look around smell taste hear
or whatever like do you see your nose at
the bottom of your vision these sort of
things like do and if you do that in a
dream because you train your
subconscious mind to do such you you
were actually to be like oh it's not oh
[__] this is a dream and so if you can
chill yourself on excitement and like
you don't instantly wake up out of that
you're able to apparently walk around
fly around control your dreams and this
is a it's literally I'm telling you this
is like you can look on Reddit and
there's hundreds and hundreds of
thousands of people who do this that was
a exaggeration of the number I don't
know but it's literally they have
protocols within the government like
there's CIA documents FBI documents I've
laced through the the CIA ones and they
literally talk about how they they have
studies on lucid dreaming in the head
like I don't know if it's like [__]
agents and the lucid dreaming world or
what but it's super weird right but
anyway so you can awaken from a dream
and then control whatever you may
like that's something there's a possum
if against of that well so so I think if
you think of humans outside of like our
lineage of humans like if you think of
like different civilizations that we
have proof that we're like just
decimated by you know global
catastrophes asteroids and like clearing
clean earth I was talking about like how
history is different if you look at
different like let's say psycho
technologies like we have we have the
five senses and we use science like
science is kind of like our God of sorts
but if they have like like back then
there's a lot of different civilizations
and even in our lineage that lived in
the dream world like so shamans for
example the shaman character in
civilizations like it's you know the
person who writes on the wall and the
caves and the person who explores the
NAM of the dreamworld but like in the
consciousness world he comes back any
teaches the the people the physical
world so the shoot I lost that I'm
losing the thread lucid dreaming lucid
dreaming yeah so so so essentially it's
not it's abnormal to us especially in
the Western world right lucid dreaming
but lineages like all that like a lot of
old stories like when you read about
shamans this is the story that you hear
a lot it's like they're I think I think
this is broad generalization again no I
think a lot of the Indian people like
people who like grew up in more forests
like less civilization and condensed
together I believe that they probably
like talked to like let's say their gods
in the in the spirit spirit world it
could have been like a during lucid
dreaming like it could have been for all
we know it's like as much as you and I
as we're talking and we're like well
that's crazy you can control your dreams
like imagine there could have been a
civilization of people who are talking
in their language and they're like wait
you can't control your dreams with the
[__] what do you do for hanging hours
not you idiot
you know I mean like like that's how
different things could be and and
yeah sorry I think I floated off top now
I seem to be losing the thread a little
bit no that's okay it's it's lucid
dreaming it's you having it's like all
right Oh a world unknown honestly its
and what I think is very odd is that
within those communities like you were
saying like people who are indigenous
and sort of out there and have those
kind of traditions of lucid dreaming or
having breathing exercises where they
unloosen it together as soon as a group
or you know things like that it seems so
odd to me that those are very if you've
ever been a part of one you'd know how
spiritually and lighting it is and how
connected you can be to the people
around you even if you have no idea who
they are like I did a simple simple gosh
what kundalini yoga class or it's like
deep heavy super fast your breathing
breath work and it gets you I edit it
gets you all this stuff but it also puts
you in this crazy crazy mindset of
having extreme amounts of oxygen pushed
into your muscles and you feel like
extremely alive and you feel your senses
extremely heightened and then we started
doing the home together as a class of
like 30 people like all owning at once
and I [__] you not
you sink in or with everyone on one
common sound wow that is just an amazing
vibration and would you experience what
do you mean what do you mean sink him
like what was how is this a different
form of consciousness than normal yeah
it's it's it was a unified consciousness
it was it was like a
a soccer team that is going down the
field and they seem like they are
kicking the ball to each other with
purpose and intent and they they're all
on the same page like if one kicks the
ball like and it looks like it's going
nowhere you'll just see someone running
out of nowhere like oh I see what you're
doing yeah how did you see that and they
were both on the same positions on a
stage exactly and working together just
just like that it felt we learned a
common language we can communicate in
real time in front of other people who
don't know that common language and it
was it wasn't anything that's what's so
weird about it it was a sound that
connected yourself to everyone around
you and created a pattern of vibrations
sounds so crazy and it sounds so hard to
to grasp right and be like all right
well what's the purpose of like sound
vibrating people connecting with each
other it's something that you cannot
just be like you can't just explain to
someone you have to feel it and that's
for those people that are skeptical and
being like well I don't really care
about connecting with people and all
that stuff you don't know right if you
have not tried it you don't know what it
feels like and you don't know what
you're missing out on and who knows
maybe you don't want it right if you
know but you will feel more connected to
people you will feel feel you'll feel
more mhm
you'll have more emotion I just you know
I I'm such a why not person I'm like I
want to discover like you know like I
want to experience like whatever it like
I'm here for a fickle amount of time
like what like if I choose who I am then
I don't get to experience all these
wonderful beautiful things like thank
you if I have someone who I enjoy
hanging out with who I enjoy spending
time with who I you know I I can trust
and I trust their opinion and they're
like doing this breathing home exercise
it's just super crazy like whatever like
they're not trying to say like you need
to believe this because the
the truth I feel like we get caught up
so much with trying to like really you
know that's not truth that's not really
you know like what like what why not
just as you're here on earth choose with
your own stomach to just experience to
experience whatever you want I try to
how I overcame I wish I had a strange
fear of water that was kind of bumming
me out and I really wanted to wakeboard
in last summer I had this like I kept
like trying to build myself up because I
think about wakeboarding before the trip
I think about it and I'm like [__] I
want to do that or do that so I tried to
move from this from from being the
person who's in the boat wishing that he
was doing it so it but I tried so I
tried to move from that into like like
what would make me want to just do it
and I just kept thinking like that and
then so finally we get into the boat and
it's like Jake you wanna try and I had
this instant like hell yeah hell yes I
do and I did and I did it and I and I
loved it and in in the thing is the
thought that I had accidentally like
provided myself with was what do you
want to have had experienced at the end
of your life and like we you could
insert these things and they lead you to
you know going going into doors that you
never tried before you know like don't
just blindly follow a bunch of [__]
because you want to try everything you
know use your intellect but but I think
like exploring all of these things is
like really where life is that and I
also think that a good relation to like
what you're talking about when everybody
kinda like one consciousness one kind of
vibe we're all just home what happens we
shut down our default mode Network like
our our typical reactions are typical
thoughts are thoughts that we always
that we don't even realize that with
Rinku ik thumb yeah right are our loops
are in constant just a default mode
network is shut down in those positions
of sorts and and so you don't have
thoughts about what you're doing you're
just doing this is kind of like think
back Brandon - the first time that you
fell in love like weather was really
love or not when you're a kid you're 15
you're 13 whatever and you're like oh my
gosh I've never felt this for a person
is this love this is love Oh what it was
is your present you're not thinking of
the future you're not regretting the
past
not thinking of what you need to wear to
school tomorrow to impress people
because you you're just present you're
laughing you're not thinking about we
should say you're just saying it you
were truly present for the first time
that's when you're experiencing love so
I think some of our most powerful
moments that that can be attained as as
humans are when we shut up and get out
of the way and we just try and we just
we try by choosing to let go in a sense
so so Christians in any time I say
Christians listeners is I'm just using
as a super broad example I'm nothing
like just trying to describe people I'm
generalizing and I'm so aware of that be
aware for me I'm a [__] DJ but a but
a so so Christians so like we you know
we're doing Kundalini Yoga and we're
stretching our bodies and if somebody
walked by who was like a Christian for
example they might look in the window
and and people are going home and
they're in your book what the [__]
but like the thing about prayer a lot of
like people in other religions when
you're praying and there's everybody
praying and you guys all kind of have
connected to this like the pastor has
given his sermon he's given his his
here's what we're kind of thinking about
so every person that remembers kind of
brought up to the same thought like what
we're learning today about courage and
individualism and you know whatever like
we're learning them about this this
amazing thought that feels good when you
articulate it we're all getting together
and we're connecting to the same feeling
the vibe per se so when everybody has
their eyes closed and they're praying
like if you lock into it and you just
say [__] you let's try it let's use my
imagination
yeah let's like it look you know just
like when you were a kid when you used
your imagination you pretend pretend not
do I feel this innately do does this
magically just light up a thing in my
chest
no man pretend for just be like what
would it feel like if I did you know
experience like okay so they're saying
this like really just shut up you know
just shut up and let yourself experience
whatever you know shut down your your
constant train of thoughts it brings you
into the present moment and then later
you can choose like I want to take that
forward or I believe that or I don't
believe that or I'm going to do some
more research
tor but I think that I was just a human
you know the spiritual ape the spiritual
being riding around in an Apes body we
should we should allow ourselves to
experience things uh you know without
identifying with them yeah like just
just just try it out so like the UM
thing I think just it like you try it
out and you're like dude it's so I'm
different it's crazy like it's it's
awesome it's whatever like I definitely
learned the experience of trying not
only new things abstract things just
trying things in general that like just
don't even sound like me or something
that I would do in my lifetime but have
been presented to me because of the fact
that I was to go hiking all the time
still I haven't gone recently cuz when
it was done over but back at it soon but
I would love like going hiking and then
you just you know you just kind of see
like a like a nice like cliff face or
like a boulder like a big boulder you're
like climb that mm you know there was
one specifically I was hiking with my
fiance and we were like down in this
like little Gorge area and I look up and
there's just like this Pride Rock
looking rock like rock that was like
halfway up a mountain and but like the
hike up up to it it was like a free
climb and it just looked gorgeous from
like I could imagine what it looked like
from that view it was just all open it
was like whoa like you get crazy view if
you saw from up there and I remember
thinking in life you can always look at
you can always look at that mountain or
you can look from that mountain you'll
never know what it is to look you'll
always know what it is to look at it
with with question and
excitement and and a lack of
understanding but you'll never know what
it's like to look from it if you don't
go up and climb it try it get there and
understand and go huh the view is kind
of shitty or holy [__] I love this view
I never knew I could love yoga like this
like this is the most amazing thing I've
ever felt but there's something to be
said about the work that you have to put
in because if there was a helicopter in
that situation that just came down
picked you up put you on top of it you'd
be like yeah that's pretty nice yeah
it's like if you're like oh it's gonna
take me eight and a half hours but you
get to the top it's different right you
know like you just live the life you
lived the experience of getting to the
top not just got to the top that for
some reason I was stuck in my head there
so long like yeah you can either look at
it or you can look from it it was Kevin
saying in my head you can look at it or
you can look from it I like kept walking
in that little Gorge and I was like hey
can we turn around real quick I want to
climb that and she was like go climb it
then like I don't care yeah and I was
like all right cool
and I just like went and climbed it and
I was like I was so worth it that was
just how'd it look from there it was
indescribable
yes it's indescribable some of the
things that that's why I love hiking so
much you're like going on those jogs and
everything like that we see some crazy
crazy crazy views that are just it takes
you so far out from society and from
your normal life
it seems so crazy that you can like wake
up one day go drive like four hours go
hike this crazy insane mm-hmm vu
landscape see a bear see whatever one
wants your bear I don't want to see a
bear either but you might I don't know
be prepared but prepare and there'd
blared prepared bad jokes but
but yeah it's it's uh yeah it's you
should go out and try it
absolutely dude it's just be like yes
man do you think yes yes man yes and
it's do things that I had a Rebecca
wildest on the podcast and she had this
thing she's like aha I always say take
me to a place where I feel small and I
was like oh that's Savage and that is
such an awesome yeah because like it's
just a reminder like so it's so like on
my run at the end of my run there's this
big log that's from like 1917 or
something and they have like a chunk of
it that's cut out and they put like the
like it was the this this old at this
year like they have like the markers on
it it's like a on display as you come
into our town but on my runs I was walk
and I was run and I hit it it's my it's
my like end like I hit it and I'm like
okay it's my insignificance like it
reminds me because like a lot of times
when I'm running I like amping myself up
like you're a savage you're a beast you
got this a savage [__] like you
got this like yeah you're Marathon
around or whatever and then I get to the
log I'm like you're all so insignificant
impermanence you know and it's this old
law just reminds me there's one last
forever you will know right like this
was here before you and it's you aren't
more important than it that's not how it
works you know it's but I think that
having those you know it's kind of like
who likes you know the stoic sort of
thinking and you know you know make us
maybe a little Buddhism thinking like
just feeling insignificant and not like
getting so caught up and like you know
cuz even like ascending a mountain and
getting the top there is an asset of
like I did it I did this awesome there's
also an aspect when you got the top
where you let go of the eye and you're
like I don't know and this is amazing I
don't know why it's just breathtaking
you just you just get out of the way and
allow that that situation that view like
all of your eyesight from left and right
up and down so good aim yeah and it's
but it's just so nuts that 9 out of 10
people will probably get to the top and
immediately pull out their phone and
take a picture of mmm
what they've got as hopes that they will
I don't know if anyone even looks back
at the pictures maybe they'll show them
to friends like look at the hike I did
this past weekend but six years down the
road are you still looking at that or do
you more remember so the memory of you
and your friend getting for this I'll
what about the smell you can't I mean I
do the memories cream I do a really
weird thing I know it's pretty gross but
I always most people don't know this at
all but I usually always get to the top
of a mountain I see a little piece of
rock or a dirt and I grab it I touch it
that touch my tongue you taste you I
taste it hell yeah I like it's a very
weird thing but like I'm like have you
consciously thought about it like we're
just kind of like I feel I don't know I
did it one time because I had my hand
down and I'm like oh that's and and some
reason I was like trying to get
something out of my mouth and I was like
yeah hmm that's what the top tastes like
and I like did I do that each time now
right well I feel that I mean I do a lot
of weird [__] myself that I might it
tastes like at the top yeah
yeah [__] don't know what it
tastes like know what it tastes like and
now when we here to make some dough
beats and write some some shitty raps
you can now say you [__] don't
know what it tastes like add them up
I've I don't eat the dirt at the top
Brandon
we've talked about eating dirt and
consciousness and being aliens and being
organic boot loaders and being conscious
beings and paying spiritual Apes
and just kind of explored some thought
experiments um I thought it was a great
conversation I'm glad that you came over
today I'm glad that uh I'm glad that we
were able to like talk about just the
corona virus and like also lead into
like a regular talk because it's
something like I said I'm you know I
can't you know I am nervous about the
corona virus I am I don't know exactly
what to do about this podcast I really
want to keep going but I want to make
sure everybody's healthy and safe and I
don't want to do the wrong thing so I'm
just trying and thanks for letting me
try
and thanks for being here to [__]
with me and also thanks for listening
because I hung out with a lot of humans
just a talkative dead bro and just like
I have all these concepts that I've just
been like taking notes on the day but em
yeah it was a good time
I appreciate it too man thank you yeah
we'll have to do we'll have to do some
more and especially we can do some one
zoom Pappa zoom podcast but especially
just coming over to create because
you're one of the listener if you're
dying to get around people and I'm not
fetal ha and I think this is against the
law so keep that in mind but maybe just
you know please take care of your mental
health like that like it's so serious
you know mental health is not something
that's like a little sign thing that you
only deal with when you're feeling super
[__] depressed and scared like deal
with it now if you're afraid of your
mental health if you're if you are
concerned with your lack of being around
people just please limit your contact
but you know choose a couple people to
be around choose a couple people to to
fill your life with and make sure you're
valuing those conversations take extra
precautions and that sort of thing like
look at look at our life and our health
as full circle for yourself and for
others and go from there absolutely and
if I have one piece of advice for this
sort of coming to an end and you know
hopefully it is coming to an end and
kind of lifting this is a new
opportunity to become a better you where
we've all been secluded we've all been
pushed into a corner of kind of a harsh
situation and you don't know what mental
struggles people are going through this
is a chance to be the nicest know most
just very very nice person I guess I
don't even know what the word is to say
right now but it's just me just be nice
be overly nice and
know that this is a time where you can
enrich the community you can build
relationships stronger than ever you can
you can change the world for the better
in a great way and also establish some
very strong attributes about yourself
keep drinking water keep working out
keep don't want to move drink that water
drink that water take a big old deep
belly breath and say I love yourself
hello you have a great day
every day just think to yourself today I
am saying out loud - today I'm going to
have a great day I believe I'm gonna
have a great day today will be a great
day let's go pretend imagine see what it
looks like we're gonna die I feel like
my podcast is gonna turn it like so much
positive content right at the meeting
where it's just like no do you hang up
hang up I love it though because I like
the guests are always like yeah I do
want to say this like a little
encouraging I love it so good well I
like how you start off with it but yeah
let you write let you write out alright
bro I appreciate you listeners have a
good rescued a pizza listeners take a
look around look at your surroundings
just be aware make sure you're not
mindlessly consuming too much content
even if it's my content I'd rather have
people living fulfilled lives than just
consuming my [__] so I hope this stuff
helps if you don't mind if you have a
second just after you get present of
course like share subscribe send to a
friend if you did like it send a clip
post a clip whatever you like just get
the word up take care yourself
you